Speaker SPEAKER_00:  Hey, I'm out at a ravine. What's this thing that spans across it?
Speaker SPEAKER_02:  That is how you get to my sector.
Speaker SPEAKER_00:  No kidding. Well, let me hike over.
Speaker SPEAKER_02:  Well, it's locked up in mainly four emergencies. I've never actually used it.
Speaker SPEAKER_02:  Rangers use it from time to time, but that's it.
Speaker SPEAKER_01:  Help! Oh God, it's an emergency!
Speaker SPEAKER_02:  Oh, really?
Speaker SPEAKER_01:  Yeah, I got eyes on a tornado. I gotta get out of here.
Speaker SPEAKER_03:  A tornado in the heart of the Rockies?
Speaker SPEAKER_01:  Yes!
Speaker SPEAKER_03:  Holy moly, I need to call this in! Tom, Two Forks sees a tornado! He says he needs an evac into my sector. It's a meteorological impossibility? There haven't been tornadoes in the Greater Yellowstone Region in a hundred million years? You're gonna need him to stay and take a detailed personal account, even if it means giving his life? Okay, I'll tell him.
Speaker SPEAKER_03:  Sorry, Hank. No dice.
Speaker SPEAKER_00:  Man.